Please contact turkision@gmail.com for any inquiries
No living being was harmed
during the filming of this series.
Episode 110
Commander Samagar.
They have gone in this direction.
I will separate your flesh
from your bones, Osman.
I swear by Erlik Khan.
Walk.
You've got yourself
into big trouble, Osman Bey.
Adults have great concerns, Hadrat Sultan.
Do not worry at all.
This is a matter you did
not have to get involved.
You will lose your
little tribe because of me.
Your loss of position and rule did not
make you lose any of your pride.
What are the Alps
busy with, Osman Bey?
We got off the horses.
And now we stand like this.
You have been with them for many years.
But you never knew the Mongols.
For this reason, you had to fight them.
They are skillful in tracking.
What you said is just criticism.
You didn't answer my question, Osman Bey.
Alps turned the horseshoes.
So they will think we've gone to
the opposite direction.
However, we will not go on horseback.
Surviving the Mongols
by running away is difficult.
We must mislead them, at least.
Will they believe this?
At least, that's how we'll divide them up.
Is everything ready?
Are the Alps ready?
Yes, my Bey.
Okay.
Alps!
Get rid of the horses and follow us!
Hadrat Sultan
Konya Palace
My uncle who sits at home
and waits for his death...
runs away when the day
comes to kill him, right?
Osman, Hadrat Sultan.
The reason he came
here was to take Mesut.
He also took his son from the palace.
- Also...
- Vizier!
This is my last warning to you.
Never come to me with excuses again.
Take an army with you.
Kill my uncle and Osman
and bring them to me.
However...
if you lie...
I'm going to hang you
in the square, Saveli.
Commander Samagar.
The traces point in this direction.
These traces do not lead to Yenişehir.
Osman and his Alps
will not go in this direction.
Samagar.
The traces point in this direction.
Since when you can say your opinions?
Look.
These are the front footprints.
They are deeper.
The horse's head is in front, that's
why it's heavy, you idiot.
Osman must have turned
the horseshoes!
Bring the poison arrows.
We will split to two parts.
You will go in the direction
indicated by the traces.
The rest will come with me.
You will kill Osman and Mesut
wherever you see them.
Hadrat Sultan, we make you walk
like this without a horse.
Sorry.
I will decide on this when I
ascend the throne, Osman Bey.
I don't judge now, anyway.
We couldn't have gone where we were
going with the Mongols following us.
For this reason, bear a little.
Good.
Osman Bey.
I want you to answer me honestly.
I've known you for years.
Let's say you succeeded...
and made me ascend the throne.
What will you ask from me?
When you ascend the
throne of the East...
the gates of the West will
be opened to me.
You will support me in conquests.
But these things will
happen in the future.
If we talk about the current situation...
your presence...
will weaken the power of
the Sultan Mother.
Everything that happens is because of her.
Her greed for power made
my nephew hostile to me.
She took my throne from me.
What did she take
from you, Osman Bey?
My castles...
and...
she gave them to the infidels.
I will take my properties
back and cut off her head.
You'll take it, I promise.
When I ascend the throne, I will
stand behind you.
You will recover many times
what you lost, Osman Bey.
My Sultan!
Alps!
My Sultan, hold on.
Hold on.
You are...
Come on, Alps.
Everyone will take their provisions.
Bala Hatun...
it's good that we survived the day, but...
What are we going to
do tomorrow?
We must find a way, Bengi Hatun.
Do not worry.
How do I not worry?
This is not only your problem.
I also want to do the best I can.
If you wish, give us one of the carriers and
let us distribute to the neighboring tribes.
Yes, Bala Hatun.
Let's do something.
Okay.
Good.
Distribute the supplies quickly.
We must dispel the fear of the people.
Having you by our side has made
me very happy, Bengi Hatun.
Our rivalry remains between us.
But this is a different matter.
Gürbüz Alp.
Hand that carriage over to Bengi Hatun.
It will be distributed to
neighboring tribes.
Not possible.
We'll take the supplies.
I no longer have
confidence in Bengi Hatun.
What's that talk, Malhun Hatun?
We are all doing our best for the people.
I say I will forget what
you did to me and help you.
Look what you say.
Have you forgotten who you were standing
behind a while ago, Bengi Hatun?
Cerkutay.
We'll take the cart. (carriage)
Gürbüz.
Give me the cart.
Stop it, Gürbüz.
- Right away, Gürbüz.
- I told you to stop, Gürbüz.
I came, Osman.
Samagar, whom you put in prison,
will make this world your prison.
You shouldn't have come.
I'd come to you, anyway.
You will be my revenge.
As for my job, it's to get Mesut's head.
Give it to me so that I may kill
you without skinning you.
We never turn away from
those who turn to us
Never.
I know how to take him, Osman.
Come on, come on, let's see.
Hadrat Sultan, be patient.
You will live, you will live.
Alps!
I am going with the
Sultan, please, protect us.
Don't let any them attack us.
- We'll get out of here alive.
- Thank you, my Bey.
- Baysungur.
- My Bey.
- Protect us.
- My Sultan.
Attack!
If Mesut and Osman run
away, I will kill you all.
Not possible, Bala, I never
trust this woman
We can't hand her the supplies.
Acting like this won't help.
- If we don't trust her now...
- I said no, Bala.
I've said my final word, we're the
ones to ride the cart
I didn't say my final word, Malhun.
Since yesterday, you've changed
a lot, Bala Hatun.
What did Sultan Mother promise you
so that you started talking loudly?
My voice was
always very loud, Malhun Hatun.
You're the one pretending not to hear it.
Weigh the words you say, or I'm
going to start something.
Nothing stops you.
Is this how you carry out
your mission, Frigg?
How did Malhun get access to
those supplies?
Why did I put you there?
I will learn it, don't worry.
Sultan Mother.
She says she will learn that.
The ladies have turned my move
into nothingness!
Nothingness.
I don't want any mistakes, Frigg.
I promise you, Sultan Mother.
I will correct this
mistake.
You will fix it, of course.
Otherwise, there will be no such
thing as an agreement.
No convoy will reach Yenişehir.
You will destroy all the goods you find.
Sultan Mother.
Not being able to take
supplies isn't the end.
The supplies will be the end of them.
What's going on in your mind?
Leave it, Bala Hatun.
Malhun Hatun thinks of herself
as the protector of all people.
She can't hear us anymore.
Gürbüz Alp.
Take the carriage to Bengi Hatun, and
that's my last word.
I'm the one who will deliver this cart.
This is my last word!
Cerkutay, come on!
Then...
- Bala.
- Don't, Ayşe.
Don't ever utter a single word.
I can't come to the tribe
angry like that.
I will go to the khanqah.
What is happening?
Don't you! We promised our Bey.
We'll pull back.
Well, brother.
What promise did you make to your Bey?
If your promise to your master is that
you won't die, you won't keep your promise.
My Bey said "Don't come before you
have brought Samagar's head."
Your Bey has left you behind.
This is war.
The adults flee and
the young become bait.
Come on, you dog.
Come on, come on.
You are Samagar's prey today.
I will not leave any of my Alps
behind.
Be patient, my Sultan.
Alps, back off.
How long will you stay on the run, Osman?
Do you want your time to come?
Come to me, I'm here.
Attack!
Allah is great!
My Bey, we have aimed all our arrows at
them and they still come!
We'll stop here and meet in the cave,
which is in the region of Guragac.
The Sultan will be with me.
Come on, let's go.
Quick, quick, get the horses.
Spread out in all four
directions, look everywhere.
Osman and Mesut
will be found before sunset.
When Mother Sultan...
made me and Olof sit at the same table...
then I drew my path alone, my Sheikh.
However, the matter of
Osman Bey is different.
Its pain is in my heart.
These are the reasons
why I am walking alone.
A Muslim cannot walk alone, Turgut Bey.
He unites...
under the banner of the Muhammad.
As for those who fall into heedlessness
and throw themselves...
in a different way
lose their way.
In the era of happiness (the era when
Muhammad was alive, in Islam)
one of the heathens...
attempted to cause a mess between the
Muhajireen and the Ansar.
The number of Muhajireens wasn't
many, but now their number has increased.
They became more than us.
They are trying to control us.
When we returned to Medina...
the owners of the land and
the royals united...
and they said they will expel Muhajireens.
When the words of this man
reached Muhammad...
Umar was also there.
He said "Allow me to strike the
neck of this infidel."
He asked permission from Muhammad.
He wanted to pay the penalty for
this hypocrite who spreads sedition.
However...
The Messenger of Allah objected to
the request of Umar.
Leave it, Umar, he said.
"I don't want people to think that
Muhammad kills his friends."
The Messenger of Allah acted
cautious...
so that...
heathens wouldn't reach their goals.
Osman Bey accepted the offer of
Sultan Mother and gave her the castles...
he acted with serenity.
However, the time has come.
Now, we need the wrath of our Umar.
Do you have this anger...
Turgut Bey?
Do you have the anger...
that boils over for the cause?
For the cause of upholding
the word of Allah...
Will you be able to control yourself...
Turgut Bey?
In The Name of Allah, most
gracious, most merciful.
Will you be able to root out the infidels
from the fortress of the Turkmens, Turgut Bey?
Think about this very carefully.
Hey, hey!
Come on, bear it, bear it, bear
it, brother.
Şamil.
Lie down, my Sultan.
- Give us water.
- Here, my Bey.
My Sultan.
Come on.
Sultan.
Sultan is not someone who
falls like this because of one arrow.
My Bey, are you saying the
arrow might be poisoned?
Let's open the wound and let's see.
Brothers.
Sultan isn't good.
I don't want to say that, however...
If Sultan dies, what will we do then?
May Allah forbid, my brother.
My Bey worked hard for his moves.
He must live.
In the name of Allah.
His breath is not good.
My Sultan.
My Sultan!
Aykurt! Tell my Sheikh at once!
Your command, my Bey.
Come on.
My Sultan!
No! No!
No!
Osman.
Osman!
How dare you kidnap Mesut?
You've crossed your limit this time.
You've gone too far.
I'm listening to you, Bengi Hatun.
Today I offered a little
help to Bala Hatun.
Malhun Hatun disagreed.
It's clear that Bala won't make
way for Malhun anymore.
You are a smart Hatun.
But apparently, Bala is also smart.
She listened to what I said.
She did.
She is now coming to the
khanqah to see her father.
I wanted to go ahead and
give you this good news.
Not only that, Sultan Mother.
Whatever is talked about in Osman's
palace from now on, we will hear it too.
Alçiçek's helper Esma is now
in the Yenişehir palace.
Very nice.
Tell Esma to wait for news from me.
You say we will flare up
the fire more.
We will...
so that this fire will turn all of
Osman's dreams into ashes.
Let's heal this wound.
Come on, in the name of Allah!
Come on!
My Sultan.
My Sultan!
Şamil, look at this.
His eyes are completely red, while
their surroundings are yellow.
Don't you know about this poison?
Don't you know?
I'll find out, my Bey.
My Bey, this is scorpion poison.
I know the herb that will heal it.
It rarely grows in this
area, but I will find it.
Why are you waiting?
Don't come back before you find that herb.
Şamil, if you don't find it, we will lose
Sultan.
Hold on.
Söğüt
Bala Hatun.
Sultan Mother.
Would you have gone without seeing me?
Stop, let me look at you.
What made you angry?
Only my Sheikh can
calm the anger inside me...
I wanted to go there first.
I'd see you by later, of course.
Even I'm not at Sheikh Edebalı's
level, I'm also a good listener.
Tell me, what's your problem?
You were right.
I thought everyone was like me.
Is it Malhun Hatun?
She ignored my words
today in front of everyone.
I will not forgive her for this.
She raises her voice to
suppress your voice.
But you must not take any step back.
I will invite all the Hatuns of the
tribesmen to the Inn tomorrow.
You should come too.
Come, too, so they can see
who the Head Hatun of Yenişehir is.
Will it be useful?
He will open his eyes immediately, and
his wound will heal quickly, my Bey.
My Allah.
My Bey, he should drink this.
Help me, Baysungur.
Take it, it's done.
Slowly, slowly.
It shows its effect, doesn't it, my Bey?
His breath is getting
better little by little.
Praise be to Allah.
Thank Allah!
My Sultan.
Breathe.
Breathe deeply.
Are you okay now?
We had better days, Osman Bey.
Thank you, Şamil.
Thank you, my Bey.
Mashallah.
Hadrat Sultan.
Don't worry, we will take you to a safer
place than here and right away.
The one who did this to you is
the Mother Sultan herself.
You should know this.
I know, I know, Osman Bey.
Samagar trusts her.
Saveli too.
If they did not exist, then the
Sultan Mother would have no power.
I will destroy them all.
Tell me now...
How can I destroy the power
of the Sultan Mother?
How?
There is a seal, Osman Bey.
She has her full power from that seal.
Seal?
How?
If I take that seal...
can I stop her?
If the seal is not present...
She will no longer have any power.
Mother Sultan!
Traitor, traitor!
I will cut off Turgut's head
with my own hands!
When Sultan Mother learns that
he is the one who took the supplies...
Don't, don't, Frody!
You won't say anything to anyone!
You will not say anything
to Sultan Mother!
Will what that traitor did
remain unpunished?
How many of our soldiers
have been killed, Dan?
He will pay for this!
He will! I promise you.
But not now.
When the time comes, we will kill
him with our own hands.
But not now.
When? when?
When? When?
When?
May you belong to who is skilled in war.
How long have you been
dreaming of royalty?
Since the blood of my heroes spilled
on the ground in the conquests years ago.
Isn't Öktem's blood enough?
Whatever it was, you gave possession to
whoever was not present at the conquest.
I've always been by
your side, Osman Bey.
You chose this.
No, this is not
permissible, I cannot bear this.
If you want to expel me from my country...
I will not leave a home to anyone.
Kutan.
Your command, my Bey.
Send messengers to the Beys
of Bilecik, Karacahisar and Kulucahisar.
Let them line up their armies.
I, Turgut, won't leave the kingdom of the
Turks under the shadow of the infidels.
May Allah bless you, my Bey.
Your command.
Come on.
Söğüt
Where is Mesut?
Where could Osman
hide him?
Speak!
If you don't tell me all of
Osman's secret places...
you won't be able to breathe.
Ask your men.
Are you making fun of me?
Are you in pain?
If you don't speak, you will suffer more.
You won't get any word from me.
Summon him.
I will find that seal no matter what.
And I will take everything Sultan
Mother have.
My Sheikh.
Osman Bey.
My Sheikh
Sultan Mesut is fine.
He's fine, don't worry.
Bala.
Are you well?
I'm good.
Mashallah.
May Allah heal you, Sultan Mesut.
Osman Bey.
Dervishes are outside.
Now I know why they are required.
My Sheikh, Söğüt is the safest place.
The most unattractive place is the khanqah.
The dervishes will let Sultan Mesut
inside without anyone seeing him.
Sultana Mother is so arrogant that she...
will not see what is in front of her eyes.
She won't come to the khanqah.
Good thing you thought of it.
We are pleased to host you in our
humble place, Sultan Mesut.
But if you are looking for the comfort you
used to feel in the palace...
You will not be able to find it.
Our bed is made of goatskin.
Be aware of this.
It's fine, Sheikh Edebalı.
Your goatskin bed...
is better than those in the palace.
At least my life is in good hands.
Thank you.
Bala will solve this.
We will destroy Sultan Mother.
Osman Bey.
Are you talking about getting to İsmihan
and taking the seal from her?
Don't worry at all.
Bala will deal with it...
without making her feel anything
Don't worry, Sultan Mesut.
Come on, we have to go
without wasting time.
I leave you in the safety of Allah first and
then in the trust of those I trust the most.
Osman Bey.
Where are you going?
I had told you that I would
cut off two heads.
And now I'm going to cut
the first of them.
My Sheikh.
Bala.
Come on, Frigg
But he thinks you're Marta.
Obviously...
He will die with this
information, Sultan Mother.
But this information...
won't help him at all.
But your actions...
will be enough to make him talk.
What is that?
Is it...
insects that will make all of
Yenişehir's supplies toxic?
You damned people.
Look, look.
Look, my Sultan.
He's already started talking.
I think we should try it here first.
Let's see if it has the
power to make Osman's Alp talk.
İnegöl Castle
We did business with you
once, Turgut Bey, that's right.
But why do you keep bringing us together?
Did it end
like this, Uraz Bey?
Is everything completed?
What is not done yet, Turgut Bey? Tell us.
We did not get our castles.
We did not clean the
lands from the infidels.
We didn't do anything.
Don't, Turgut Bey.
When the infidels were in the castles,
we were the ones who confronted them.
You were sharing your food with
the infidels then.
Also, did you not keep silent, Turgut Bey?
You keep repeating the same thing.
That food was poison to me.
Specifically for me.
Now, tell me.
While we are working for our lands...
Where is Osman Bey?
Tell me.
Where is Öktem Bey?
Is there anyone pursuing
this cause but me? Tell me.
If the issue is the conquest, then our
souls are sacrificed on this path.
Tell us what we'll do.
May Allah bless you.
First...
We will strike the necks of the infidels
who are in the castles...
and we clean them from
our lands forever, Inshallah.
Olof's dogs see us as too
weak to think of attacking them.
We will defeat them through
this arrogance.
Now listen to me carefully.
My Alps will be stationed
next to the castle.
You will open the gates when
you are sure of the measures.
Then, we will sweep Olof and his dogs
from our homeland, Inshallah.
Now tell me, Beys.
Are you with me?
Beys are with me.
Yenişehir, Osman Bey's Palace
Will Bala Hatun stay in the khanqah?
This is what it looks like, Ülgen
I didn't get it! Why did this happen?
Don't talk about it too much.
Their anger is still fresh, however...
Bengi Hatun wanted to do
something. What's wrong with that?
Perhaps it would have
been fixed like this.
This isn't that big.
Ülgen.
Malhun Hatun.
I...
It's not my problem, however...
I was so sad, so...
Since you were so sad...
you should have gone after Bala.
Gather your things and get
out of here as soon as possible.
But...
Are you kicking me out now?
Stop, Malhun.
If you're going to leave Ülgen
go, but I won't.
I said my last word, Bala.
Ülgen, you're going.
But I haven't said my last word yet.
Let's talk outside then.
Draw your sword and come.
Oh! Don't fight for me!
I'll go!
I will go!
You played so good.
You acted really well
that I believed you too.
You are brilliant.
It's enough if Sultan Mother and Bengi
believe it.
She believed that she was determined
to make this fire so big.
I almost passed out.
Praise be to Allah!
Will you take a look at me?
Is it possible that we
leave you, Ülgen?
You won't leave me, right?
- Calm down!
- I got really scared.
I was confused.
Sultan Mother has sworn to
cause discord between us.
It doesn't look like
she's going to stop.
Then let's deceive her.
Yes, so be it.
Let her think she's done it
until she's relieved and stops.
Fine, but let's do it in a place
that makes everyone believe that game.
She is gathering the Bey's wives tomorrow,
and she has invited me too.
This is the best time to take the seal.
Are we going to be able to take it
out of all those Hatuns?
She must have something
important like that with her.
What if we go to her room at night and
take it while she's asleep?
But I'm not the one who's going in.
Sultan Mother will kill me.
There's no need for this, Ülgen, I know
how we're going to take it.
Your deadline for İnegol has expired.
But I see that Sultan Mother behind
whom you take refuge is not here.
So is your friend Olof.
Don't worry! I will talk to him.
Will you do it
by sitting with him at the same table?
I will charge you for this later.
But now the matter is different.
Mongols who are in Konya are the
biggest supporters of Sultan Mother.
Now they will come to break us.
- We were one...
- Since when we were one?
First, we shall behead
Commander Samagar who will come here.
Then we'll kick Olof
out of the castles.
How are we going to
cut off Samagar's head?
You are the one who will do this.
Standing next to the Sultan
Mother will help you do this.
Tell .
Sultan Mesut is with me.
I knew you wouldn't come
back without anything...
to Sultan Mesut.
Tell Sultan Mother that Sultan Mesut
is in my possession.
I keep him in
the cave at Guragac.
You'll tell her we've taken
action against her.
And she will send us Commander Samagar.
And when he comes to us, I will cut off his head.
Okay.
Get started. There's something
I'm going to talk to him about.
You left me alone in the most
difficult moments I went through.
I lost many martyrs because of you.
Many weapons were lost.
I did not complete many conquests.
And if I'm talking to you now...
This is because my
call is greater than my anger.
The situation for me is
no different from this.
Everything I do is for my calling.
Finish it.
Victory is definitely ours.
You can be sure.
Is Alçiçek okay? Have you ever seen her?
She was so saddened by
what Aktemur Bey did.
But she is strong and knows
how to get up after a fall.
Of course, Alçiçek is a strong girl.
But those who made her fall will
regret it deeply... deeply!
Esma! Did Aktemur call Alçiçek "sister"?
If he had said that, Alçiçek would have
knocked him down immediately.
Right?
That's what they deserve.
Look at the dough and I'll do this.
Why do you look like that?
Am I not allowed to look?
It is forbidden, my brother.
Come on, get out and go on your way
I'm not going out... I'm not going out.
I'm thinking, could this happen?
Why not?
It can't happen... nor should it happen.
No, it can happen.
I told you, it can't happen! Don't
overstep your bounds.
Ülgen Hatun, would you please give
me some food, if possible?
Not Ulgen Hatun!
You'll call her sister Ulgen!
Hatun!
Sister, sister I'm telling you!
Like this: Sister Ulgen! Sister Ulgen!
Do you understand?
That's enough, man! Shut up!
I understand!
But you also should understand this:
You will have no food from me anymore.
Did you understand?
Get out of my kitchen!
- I didn't say it to you.
- Of course you didn't!
- Fill it, fill it.
- I will.
I will enjoy this.
- Fill it up... Fill it up abundantly
- Well, I'll fill it up.
Thank you.
Sogut
I see that you are very disturbed,
Hadrat Mother Sultan.
And this is despite the fact that the
Byzantine commanders support you.
I hope you are not in trouble.
I never lose, Turgut Bey.
And it sounds like you're mad at
me for this Olof issue.
But this is the policy.
Everyone sits together at the same table.
That table was poisonous for me.
I would never sit with him, but...
Anyway... I heard that Osman
took Sultan Mesut from your hand.
Looks like you lost this time.
Osman has ended himself with this move.
Samagar will bring Mesut to me.
He's following Osman now.
Samagar.
Inshallah.
What if I tell you I know where they are?
What does this mean, Turgut Bey?
Do you know it but not telling me?
Or do you want something in return?
Don't you forget that
I protected your castle from Osman.
There are things more valuable than Inegol.
For example, your throne and
your authority...
...and that's why you want Sultan Mesut
so badly.
What do you want?
120 horses and 200 swords
will go to Ingol under your command.
Right now.
Why? Is there a danger?
Danger can come from everywhere.
For example, you might
try to put Olof on Ingol's throne.
Being careful is a good thing.
Avci Bey.
Turgut Bey will be given
120 horses and 200 swords
Immediately.
Eyvallah.(Thank you)
I am listening to you now.
They keep Sultan Mesut
in a cave in Guragac.
But tomorrow they will change location.
You'd better hurry up.
How do you know?
After fighting together all these years...
You know it's not hard for me to know.
First, I heard Mesut.
Then I checked the caves,
and then I saw him with my own eyes.
He was there.
Turgut Bey.
Did you just sell Osman for 120 horses?
Osman is not even worth 5 horses.
I am done with him.
It's all between you and him now.
I should go now.
Goodbye.
Guragac
I will skin whoever moves!
Your end has come, Sultan!
O Right!
I decide what begins and what ends.
I will take your soul, Osman
We don't have a soul to give you.
Sogut
- Peace be upon you.
- Peace be upon you too.
Attention, Mother Sultan coming!
- Welcome.
- Thank you.
Bala Hatun.
Sit where you deserve
Go ahead.
Praise be!
You are all here, Hatuns.
How can we not come when you call,
Hadrat Mother Sultan?
Everyone is here except for Malhun Hatun,
my Sultan.
Bala Hatun, the head of Yenisehir is here.
There is no need for others.
Go ahead.
In The Name of Allah
Most Gracious Most Merciful.
Come to the kitchen.
Since I came here...
...we experienced many things
in a short time.
But there is something I noticed.
Which is the success of The Sisters.
Both in wars and market.
They run from success to success non-stop.
Of course, it's thanks to you, Bala Hatun.
Isn't it, Hatuns?
It certainly is.
Thank you.
The success belongs to...
The Sisters who do not back down
from their goal
- We're just showing them the purpose.
- You're humble.
Everything you touch blossom, Bala Hatun.
From now on, you will take care of
Yenisehir too, not just The Sisters
Come on, sisters,
let's grab the sherbet quickly
Serve Mother Sultan first.
Hey girl!
Stop.
Oh, if you serve it with this,
they'll be mad at me!
Can't you see the dust on it?
Now it shines like a mirror.
We just dodged a scolding.
You're praising The Sisters now,
that's good, but...
...I heard that someone is preventing
his daughters from joining them
Bala Hatun.
I want to join The Sisters if you agree.
First, we have to ask your mother,
Alcicek.
Do you agree, Bengi Hatun?
Of course she can join
I'd be glad that you raise her, Bala.
Eyvallah (thank you).
You have done what is expected of you,
Bengi Hatun.
Hatuns.
You too...
Listen to your Head Hatun.
My Sultan!
Oh Mother Sultan!
Open your eyes, my Sultan!
Close the door quickly,
everyone will be searched!
- Come on
- Open your eyes, Mother Sultan.
Open your eyes, Sultana Mother
Come on.
- Mother Sultan!
Mother Sultan, open your eyes.
Is she breathing?
- She is.
- We have to make her vomit.
- Come on Bala.
- Turn her around.
Mother Sultan, open your eyes.
Open your eyes, come on.
Come on!
Call Kumral Abdal quickly,
she's not vomiting
My Sultan.
We have arrived, Osman Bey!
Samagar is running away!
Alps!
Let's go, alps!
Who would dare to do such a thing?
Whoever did this...
...It is clear that they
want to play with their life.
Mother Sultan?
Do you hear me? Are you well?
Kumral Abdal.
What is happening?
Why didn't she wake up?
Say quickly, is she poisoned?
No, the concern eating Mother Sultan inside
made her weak.
But she's fine.
You should take care of
her health for a while.
In particular, she should
stay away from worry and sadness
I'll have a decent meal cooked
for our Sultan.
Esma!
Bengi Hatun.
Tell me quickly.
What is happening in the palace?
Come on, tell me.
What does Malhun say about Bala?
Say quickly, is there anything?
Come on, tell me.
Don't, Bengi Hatun.
Let's not interfere anymore.
Have you give up on your sister, Esma?
it's a game.
Bala Hatun and Malhun Hatun.
They are playing
a game on Mother Sultan.
There is more.
Come to me.
Game over Osman, my soldiers will kill you!
If I help the Mongols,
Osman will kill me.
...and if I help Osman,
Mother Sultan will kill me.
I know what I'm going to do.
Look at me.
Stop.
Hit me.
What are you saying, my Bey?
Hit me hard!
- How can I hit you my Bey?
- Come on!
Hit me like that, come on!
My Bey!
You hit like I'm your enemy, you dog!
What are you doing my Bey?
Don't touch!
Let's go.
Let's go my Bey.
We are coming, my Bey!
I am coming, Osman Bey!
Bayindir again.
Come on now.
You are setting the games...
...we fall into them, huh?
There is no such thing.
We are the ones who set the game...
We are the ones who ruin your game.
And this game will end
with me cutting your head.
You traitorous dog!
Erlik Khan's wrath will burn you, Osman.
When Ghazan Khan hears what you did...
And when he learns that you helped
Sultan Mesut...
He will turn your land into hell!
You are turning the land you pass
into hell.
But we...
...water the lands with our blood...
...in order to turn them into heaven.
This is the difference between us.
Bayindir, the head of Cavundur.
Do you see who stands against us?
I will go to the Sky God.
But your sword will cut off
your own head!
The head you cut is not mine.
It's the head of your own people!
He, who is afraid to sacrifice his head,
cannot remain free.
He, who does not pursue his cause
in order to be free, is not of us.
Look at me dog.
I am not the captive sultan in Konya.
I am not a Bey who is afraid of you.
I am the one who planted the seeds of a
country that will rule the world.
Tell the cruels that I sent to hell.
I am the nightmare of the oppressors.
And protector of innocents.
I am Osman Bey.
Bala!
You have to ask permission,
Bengi Hatun.
Bala Hatun has just left.
What is this panic about?
This is all a trap, my Sultan.
Bala is playing a game.
She came here to take the seal.
Find Bala Hatun immediately.
Bring her to me.
Alps!
Track her! Come on!
Mount now!
We're not coming back
until we catch that rebel!
Take him away.
And deliver this to its owner.
Your command, my Bey.
Ayaz!
Come closer.
Come.
Osman Bey.
I stood with you and your alps.
Spare my life.
Do you think that murder...
...is like trade?
There is no such trade.
If you support the cruels...
Then I will cut off your head.
I will give you gold.
The conquests you will make
require money
My treasury is huge.
If I killed you now...
...all your gold would be mine, right?
No my Bey.
I even risk my life while fighting
to protect you, don't you see?
How do I prove that I am loyal to you?
You are loyal, huh?
So, you are loyal.
Right now...
I will give you one chance to
show your loyalty.
No, don't get excited right away.
Listen to me first.
Mother Sultan keeps Konur as a prisoner.
You will take him from Mother Sultan
and bring him to us.
My Bey.
If I need this to earn your trust...
I'll bring Konur to you.
- Get out of my sight.
- Come on Huseyin!
Come on.
My Bey, Bala Hatun is late.
There might be something bad.
My Bey.
Thank Allah, you are fine.
We are fine, fine, fine
Come on!
Bala, game over, Bala.
Bala!
- Mother.
- Alcicek.
What is happening here?
What are you wearing?
How do you do this to me?
I don't know anything, mother.
Bala Hatun gave it to me.
Bala. Bala.
Balaaaa!
My Bey!
Bala.
Are you fine?
We are fine, we are fine, thank Allah.
Did you take the seal?
We have it.
Oh praise be!
What are we going to do now, my Bey?
We will take back the castles that are ours.
No force can stand in the
way of the Sultan's seal.
This is why I called you.
Bala Hatun, you'll take Kulucahisar castle
with Aladdin Bey.
Malhun Hatun, you'll take Karacahisar
castle with Orhan Bey.
And we will take Bilecik.
Bring it already!
Not yet, my Bey!
Yeah, it is heating up.
You'll do it in one blow, right?
- My Bey.
- What?
Are we going to take Konur secretly or?
Whether we take him secretly or not,
Osman is already fixated on me.
As to Mother Sultan,
if we make her our enemy, she'll end us!
She'll end us, Huseyin!
Come on bring it already!
It melted!
Go easy, do it quickly!
Okay my Bey.
Hey, wait, stop.
In the name of Allah, the Most Gracious,
the Most Merciful.Come on
Mother! Mother! Mother!
Enough!
Even the wound didn't hurt this much!
- My Bey?
- Huh?
Let's say we saved Konur.
Osman Bey will go to Ismihan Sultan...
...and say that you saved Konur.
He wants to set you against her.
You dowdy owl!
Speak good words for once!
"setting me against Mother Sultan"!
No way!
Bring water, come on, bring water!
Give me patience, Allah.
Here, my Bey.
I am already in pain and you...
Take it.
Until things settle...
We must stand by Osman as much as we can.
He is the one who is behind every move.
Isn't he, Huseyin?
You're right sir, my Bey...
But what if we are choosing the wrong side?
Give me patience, Allah.
Come on, go, go away, I'll rest, go!
Come on, talk, come on
Hasn't he spoken yet?
Not yet
But he will speak
You are protecting Osman.
Where is Osman?
You made a very big mistake by
taking Osman as a friend, Konur.
However, as being your Mother Sultan,
I will give you one last chance.
You will tell us Osman's secrets.
And I will offer you everything you can
have in this world.
You don't have anything you can give me.
My Sultan.
Konur will tell us Osman's secrets.
What's that bag, Avci?
My Sultan, if you allow, I'll open it som...
Cut it out, Avci!
Osman Bey sent it.
This is the end of those
who walk in your path.
I won't kill you right now just because
the things you'll say.
Your mind will be amazed at what
I will do to you when I am done with you.
Bilecik Castle.
Olof, Osman, Osman is here!
Osman?
This is my castle, Osman!
You can't enter here like that!
This is not your castle!
Commander, what happened?
Is this how you take care of the entrustment?
The only entrustment
here is your life, Osman.
This is my castle, by the order of Sultan.
It won't be that easy this time!
Soldiers!
Not just Bilecik.
Also Karacahisar and Kulucahisar...
...are now mine as they were before.
Sogut.
Stop!
Clear our way.
We shall reach to the khanqah.
Where do you come from
and where are you going?
We are coming from Allah
and to Him we shall return.
Allow us to do our job.
Search them!
- Peace be upon you
- Peace be upon you too.
Did they do something wrong, valiants?
We are obliged. We were commanded, my sheik.
We have to take a look at the carriage.
Go ahead, take a look.
This carriage is loaded with apples.
Those apples are the right of valiants.
Give apples to the heroes.
No, my Sheikh. We shouldn't eat
what's sent for the khanqah.
No, it's not the issue.
This carriage is full of apples too.
It's more than enough for the khanqah.
Come on, don't refuse the offer.
Thank you, my Sheik.
Excuse us.
Eyvallah. (No problem)
May Allah facilitate your work, valiants.
The order is clear, Olof.
We'll give castle to Osman Bey.
Not just Bilecik...
Other properties as well...
They are under our rule
as they were before
Move!
Kulucahisar Castle.
I will take back
what you took from me, Osman!
But it'll be bloody unlike the first time!
I will make banners out of your skin
and of those who stand by you!
You don't even have a homeland.
First, find a home to sleep.
But watch out...
Be careful about the wolves outside.
They may bite you.
Yenisehir Osman Bey's palace.
When will I hold the sword like you two?
Why am I not like you?
I'm weak!
Strength isn't measured
only by muscle, daughter.
How am I going to beat my enemy
if my arms are not strong, Kumral Abdal?
Look at her!
It seems that you have not heard the story
of the lion and the man of the forest.
We haven't either, Kumral Abdal.
You should tell it.
So, come on, let's sit.
Once upon a time, there was a forest man.
This forest man used to go to the forest
after every Fajr prayer.
He searches for the toughest
and best types of firewood and chops them.
And in the evening he returns
home with the firewood he has collected.
And at some point when
he was looking for firewood...
The lion, the king of the jungle,
comes roaring with all his might!
He said to the forest man:
"I am amazed at your intelligence"
The forest man said to the lion: "Why?"
The lion said: "Why would it be?
"I am the king of the jungle
and I am very strong"
"Even I can't chop those trees"
"How are you going to chop them?"
The forest man was very brave.
He said to the lion:
"O lion, I am stronger than you"
The lion couldn't take that word.
Then he said to him:
"Come on, let's wrestle and see who is stronger"
And the conflict began
The jungle man was almost defeated
But he did not give up
He said to the lion: "O king of the forests,
I have forgotten most of my strength at home"
"This fight is not fair"
The lion stops and says:
"I won't defeat a man who fights
with half his strength"
"Go get your strength and then come"
The man of the jungle knows
how arrogant the lion is.
He used it in his behalf.
He said to the lion:
"What if you run away while I'm gone?"
The lion roars!
He roars so hard that all the animals
in the forest comes out of their holes.
And he approaches the forest man,
he approaches him more.
And he says to him: "I am not afraid of anyone!"
"I am the strongest!"
The forest man is not convinced.
He said to the lion: "No, I will fight
you with half of my strength"
The lion didn't accept this situation.
The forest man pretended as if
he has another idea.
He looked at the rope lying on the ground
near them, then at the lion.
Then he says: "Okay, I'll go."
"I will fetch my strength and come, but...
...I have to make sure
you'll wait for me here"
He said to him: I will tie you to that tree
and you will wait for me until I return"
The lion says: No!
"I can't accept that!"
The forest man looks
at the lion sarcastically.
And he says to the lion:
"I knew you would run away."
The lion gets annoyed.
The lion says: "Well, tie me up,
and bring your strength, and then come"
"I will never run away"
Forest man ties the lion to the tree.
But he doesn't leave.
Rather, he hit the lion with
the stick in his hand.
He hits him non-stop.
Well, what did the lion do, Komral Abdul?
He says to forest man: "Human, either
kill me at once or let me go"
"But don't play with my ego"
"I can't stand it"
"Well, I accept that you are strong"
The lion says to the man:
"You defeated me with your mind"
But the forest man doesn't stop.
He continues hitting
him with the stick in his hand.
And he says to the lion:
"O lion, O king of the forests"
"You waste your strength
because of your ego"
"As for my strength, it increases with
the mind that my Creator has given me"
"The more you see yourself as big,
the more you will get beaten"
"And you will embarass yourself"
Meanwhile, the tiger, who is the biggest
enemy of the lion in the forest, passes by.
The tiger laughs a lot
when he sees the lion in that situation.
The tiger mocks the lion.
And the tiger says to the lion: "Huge lion!
Weren't you the biggest?"
"Look at where you are now!
Shame on you!" the tiger says.
The lion looks at the tiger for a long time.
The lion looks awful.
As if that roaring lion was gone
and a quiet cat replaced him.
The lion says to the tiger: "no matter what
you do just don't fell into a human's trap."
The lion says: "Human is strong enough to
defeat us with his mind."
If you don't know how to use your mind...
...you won't be able to defeat your enemy...
...even if you have paws like a lion.
Human thinks and moves with his mind.
Do not forget this.
I will read all your books, brother.
I'll straighten my mind first.
Then the infidels will see how
the daughter Osman Bey will defeat them.
Have the courage of a lion,
not his arrogance.
Look at the situation
of those who are arrogant.
We got back the property we lost,
Thank Allah, Osman Bey.
Yes we did.
We definitely did.
The property you caused us to lose
in the first place.
Was it my fault?
It was my fault.
However, as far as I know,
a fault can be corrected.
While you are the one
who caused all this...
...don't think that you played a big role
getting them back.
I see that
you underestimate what I've done.
No problem.
I'll consider my job a ant's job.
As long as we walk on the same path...
...being an ant is okay for me.
No.
Even if our goal is the same...
..our paths are different.
You chose this.
It was because of my anger!
I got angry because
my brother ignored me!
Anger makes a person
do things he does not want
You know this best, Osman Bey.
Yes I know.
Of course I do.
However...
It's time to pay for what you've done.
Decisions have been made.
Choices have been made.
You go your way
I'll go mine.
Anger.
Let it be as you say.
I won't walk with you anymore.
But you should know that
I have no hard feelings for you.
And I will not be against you.
For your safety...
I don't want you to stand against me.
Still, if you need anything...
Know that I will come,
even if my hands are stained with blood.
Farewell.
Eyvallah.
Sogut.
How dare you!?
What did you think of this place, Olof?
The castles you gave me...
...are Osman's now.
What are you talking about?
Don't make a fool of me.
It's your seal!
Osman took the castles with your seal!
Osman.
So you stole my stamp for this!
You gave me a promise!
Osman ordered you to
empty the castle...
...and you did nothing but leaving, huh?
It never occurred to you
to fight, did it?
Were you afraid?
Didn't you have the strength
to fight Osman?
Don't mess with me!
Your mask has fallen off, Sultan!
And your soldiers that you put under
my command have switched to Osman's sideé
What kind of trick is this?
But all of you, all of you
will witness my power!
Come to your senses, come to your senses!
Don't act stupidly!
This game is Osman's plan.
If I were to return the castles to Osman...
I would have come and kicked
you out of there myself!
Osman...
...you stole my stamp!
You stole!
You disobeyed!
I swear I will demolish Yenişehir
and that castle over your heads!
I will hang your corpse on the gates
of Yenişehir, as a lesson to the world!
Your people...
...will curse your corpse.
...they will curse your corpse.
Avci Bey, get ready.
I will rip out Osman's heart first.
We'll raid the khanqah.
Let's go.
I will come too, I will come and
make Osman pay for what he did!
You are late.
No.
You should have shown this courage before
you handed over those castles to Osman.
No!
You're not going anywhere now, Olof!
Konya Palace.
My Sultan, Osman Bey continues
to act waywardly.
My Uncle Mesut, tell me about him first,
did you find him?
Just as Samagar was about to find him,
Mr. Osman set a big trap.
He beheaded Samagar and threw his head
at the feet of our Mother Sultan.
You've crossed your limits, Osman.
My Sultan, there is more.
Osman Bey stole the stamp of Mother Sultan
and sealed his own letters.
He took the castles which are
under our Mother Sultan's rule.
Our Mother Sultan is waiting a
large army in Yenişehir.
The more I protect the rights of my people...
The more you've become disobedient, Osman.
You lit this fire, but I will stoke it.
Fear the wrath of my army, fear it,
Osman Bey.
Those who will enforce your punishment
will be at your door tomorrow.
Thank you so much for having me
in your place, Sheikh Edebali.
There is no such thing as "someone's place"
in the world, Sultan Mesut.
Especially the khanqah,
which is not owned by anyone.
It is a roof for those who have fallen,
a shadow for the exhausted,
and a refuge for the fugitive.
You lost your throne.
Our door is always open for you.
You know the best that Humans
never own the goods of world.
I have experienced this the hard way,
Sheik Edebali.
Osman Bey says he will remove
the black clouds over us
Inshallah, Inshallah.
Hurry up, come on, this way!
- What are you doing?
- Get out of my way!
- What's happening?
- This is a khanqah!
It's Ismihan Sultan's order!
Yenisehir Osman Bey's Palace
Alright, alright,
it's alright my brothers.
They say that: "A wound of sword is
an alp's closest friend."
Who says that, Cerkutay?
I have never heard of this.
They say.
People.
- Yes they do.
- Some people say it.
Where are you looking at?
When will it be ready?
None of your business.
None!
Care your own business.
Look at Aykurt instead.
Say, brother Gurbuz,
do you have children?
There was no time for marriage...
...due to running from one mission
to another, Aykurt brother.
No, no, he doesn't have time,
he doesn't have time, he doesn't have time
You said right, why didn't I get married?
It's high time.
Yes, tell this to my Bey, my Bey will
arrange your wedding in one night.
Definitely.
Who would arrange a meeting for you?
You are old!
It is now obligatory for me
to shed your blood
Let it flow, let him spill my blood!
- Gorbuz, brothers!
- Calm down, brothers.
Cerkutay! If you got thirsty in a desert...
I would drink the last water!
I wouldn't give you a sip!
She is very angry.
I am done!
I will starve!
Sister, huh? Sister?
I will make you pay for that!
Thank you, Hatuns.
- You did a great job, Bala.
- Whatever we did, we did it together.
- Isn't that right, Ulgen?
- Yes
The Chechik family also has a big stake
I'm very curious about what Bengi Hatun's
face looks like when she sees Alcicek.
So she wants to join The Sisters.
Praise be, brave girl!
Attention, Osman Bey!
- Peace be upon you
- And peace be upon you.
Go ahead
Come on.
They thought they could capture us.
But the one thing they couldn't think of
was our bravery.
We have restored our forts and castles,
with the permission of my Allah.
Come on then, enjoy your meal.
In The Name of Allah
Most Gracious Most Merciful
May I come, my Bey?
Come!
My Bey, they raided the khanqah!
Father!
What are you saying?
Sultan Mesut.
My sheik!
If they are hurt...
...I will make their lives unbearable!
Please contact turkision@gmail.com for any inquiries